MIGUEL MARCOS

Art Director

migomarco.com

MiguelJackMarcos@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/miguel-marcos instagram.com/TheAdvertisingKid (267) 323-8863 As an Art Director, my profession lies in Advertising and Branding. My intentions are to translate past experiences in Fashion, Pharma, and Consumer to drive creative breakthroughs in upcoming or dormant industries. Through my work experience in Dubai, Paris and New York City, I am grateful to have been exposed to people from all walks of life. Therefore, learning to communicate to different cultures through creative design.

SKILLS

Languages

Fluent English
Fluent Arabic
Intermediate French

Technical

InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects HTML, CSS, JavaScript Cinema4D Sketch

Hobbies

Filmmaker Basketball player Average cook

EXPERIENCE

Grey Group

Art Director

Advertising, Dec 2021 - Current New York City

Jr Art Director

Advertising, Apr 2020 - Dec 2021 New York City

Ideating concepts
Digital and print design
Illustration design
Training and supervising

Rosa Chá & JohnJohn

Brand Designer

Fashion, June - Dec 2019 New York City

Full-scale brand design
Adertising in VOGUE and Instagram
Packaging and store design
Instagram feed content creation

Leo Burnett

Art Director Intern

Advertising, Summer 2018 Dubai

McDonald's happy-meal board game ideas & designs approved GMC in-house presentation design for employee motivation McDonald's Advertisement for new fish bites

Impact BBDO

Art Director Intern

Advertising, Summer 2016 Dubai

Pitched two approved ad ideas for their biggest client (Etisalat) Designed an exit animation for Etisalat's Ads

EDUCATION

Parsons

Bachelor's Degree

Communication Design, 2015 - 2019 New York City

Motion concepts Advertising concepts Advanced typography Topics: Branding

Parsons

Study Abroad, Paris

Art, Media, & Technology, Spring 2018 Paris

Information visualisation Journalism photography Strategic management

SABIS International School

High School

Extracurricular Activities, 2012 - 2015 Dubai

Video advertisement for music event Poster design for music competition SABIS Stars advertising 2nd place Basketball MVP